overpopulated: adj. 人口多的
Lesson 47. Too high a price? Pollution is the price we pay for an overpopulated,
第47课。价格太高？污染是我们为人口过多的价格支付的价格
over-industrialized: adj. 过度工业化的
over-industrialized planet. When you come to think about it, there are only four ways you can
过度工业化的星球。当您考虑一下时，只有四种方法可以
deal with rubbish. Dump it, burn it, turn it into something you can use again.
处理垃圾。倾倒它，燃烧，将其变成可以再次使用的东西。
sheer: adj. 纯粹的，不掺杂的
Attempt to produce less of it. We keep trying all four methods. But he sheer volume of rubbish we
尝试少生产它。我们一直在尝试所有四种方法。但是他的垃圾量很大
worldwide: adv. 在全世界, overwhelm: v.   制服，使不知所措
produce worldwide threatens to overwhelm us. Rubbish, however, is only part of the problem of
在全球生产威胁着我们。但是，垃圾只是问题的一部分
polluting our planet. The need to produce ever-increasing quantities of cheap food leads to a different
污染我们的星球。需要生产越来越多的廉价食品导致不同的需求
pollution: n.   污染
kind of pollution. Industrialized farming methods produce cheap meat products. Beef,
污染。工业化农业方法生产廉价的肉类产品。牛肉，
pesticide: n.   杀虫剂, fertilizer: n.   肥料
pork and chicken. The use of pesticides and fertilizers produces cheap grain and vegetables.
猪肉和鸡肉。农药和肥料的使用会产生廉价的谷物和蔬菜。
The price we pay for cheap food may be already too high. Mad cow disease, BSE,
我们为廉价食品支付的价格可能已经太高了。疯牛病，BSE，
salmonella: n.   沙门氏菌
in cattle, salmonella and chicken and eggs, and wisteria in dairy products. And if you think you'll
在牛，沙门氏菌，鸡肉和鸡蛋中，以及乳制品中的紫藤。如果你认为你会
vegetarian: n.   吃素的人
abandon meat and become a vegetarian, you have the choice of very expensive organically grown
放弃肉并成为素食主义者，您可以选择有机种植的非常昂贵的
pesticide: n.   杀虫剂
vegetables or a steady diet of pesticides. Every time you think you're eating fresh salads and
蔬菜或农药持续饮食。每当您认为自己吃新鲜的沙拉和
insidious: adj. 暗中为害的
vegetables, or just having an innocent glass of water. However, there is an even more insidious kind
蔬菜，或者只是喝一杯无辜的水。但是，有一种更阴险的
pollution: n.   污染, urban: adj. 城市的
of pollution that particularly affects urban areas and invades. Our daily lives. And that is noise.
特别影响城市地区和入侵的污染。我们的日常生活。那就是噪音。
Berglare alarms going off at any time of the day or night serve only to annoy passers-by-end.
白天或晚上的任何时候，Berglare警报都会逐渐烦恼。
burglar: n.   窃贼, scream: v.   尖叫
Actually assist burglars to burgl. Car alarms constantly scream at us in the street and are a source
实际帮助窃贼到达伯格尔。汽车警报在街上不断向我们尖叫，是来源
profound: adj. 极度的, irritation: n.   烦躁
of profound irritation. A recent survey of the effects of noise revealed. Surprisingly,
深刻刺激。最近发现了噪声影响的最新调查。出奇，
pollution: n.   污染, incessantly: adv. 连续不断地
that dogs barking incessantly in the night rated the highest form of noise pollution on a scale.
那只狗在夜间不断地吠叫，在尺度上评价了最高形式的噪声污染。
Ranging from 1 to 7, the survey revealed a large number of sources of noise that we really dislike.
调查范围从1到7，揭示了我们真正不喜欢的大量噪音来源。
Lawn mowers whining on a summer's day. Late night parties in apartment blocks.
草坪割草机在夏天的日子里抱怨。公寓街区的深夜聚会。
Noisy neighbors. Vehicles of al-kinds. Especially large container trucks thundering through
嘈杂的邻居。Al-Kinds的车辆。尤其是大型集装箱卡车穿过
helicopter: n.   直升飞机
quiet village. Plains and helicopters flying overhead. Large radios carried round in public places
安静的村庄。平原和直升机飞过头顶。大型收音机在公共场所围绕
maximum: adj. 最大的, technology: n.   技术, contribution: n.   贡献
and played at maximum volume. New technology has also made its own contribution to noise.
并以最大音量播放。新技术还为噪音做出了贡献。
mobile: adj. 可移动的
A lot of people object to mobile phones. Especially when they are used in public places like
很多人反对手机。特别是当它们在公共场所使用时
mobile: adj. 可移动的
restaurants or on public transport. Loud conversations on mobile phones invade our thoughts or
餐馆或公共交通工具。手机上的大声对话侵犯了我们的想法或
pollution: n.   污染
interrupt the pleasure of meeting. Friends for a quiet chat. The noise pollution survey revealed
打断见面的乐趣。朋友进行安静的聊天。噪声污染调查显示
a rather spurring and possibly amusing old-fashioned source of. Noise. It turned out to be snoring.
一个相当激烈的，可能是有趣的老式来源。噪音。原来是打s。
snore: v.   打鼾, offender: v.   冒犯者
Men were found to be the worst offenders. It was revealed that 20% of men in their mid-30s snore.
发现男人是最糟糕的罪犯。据透露，30年代中期的男性中有20％的男性打sn。
staggering: adj. 令人惊愕的
This figure rises to a staggering 60% of men in their 60s. Against these figures,
这个数字上升到60多岁的60％的男性。在这些数字上
snore: v.   打鼾
it was found that only 5% of women snore regularly, while the rest are constantly woken or kept awake
发现只有5％的女性定期打sn，而其余的则不断醒来或保持清醒
trumpet: v.   吹号, partner: n.   伙伴
by their trumpeting partners. Whatever the source of noise, one thing is certain. Silence. It seems
通过他们的小号伙伴。无论噪音的来源是什么，一件事是可以肯定的。沉默。它似乎
has become a golden memory.
已经成为金色的记忆。